CYBER WEEK DEALS: SAVE UP TO 30%

CYBER WEEK DEALS: SAVE UP TO 30%

Menu icon Menu

 [

 ](https://www.soapboxsoaps.com/)

    [
    
    #### Shop bundles](https://www.soapboxsoaps.com/collections/bundles)[
    
    #### Shop by scent](https://www.soapboxsoaps.com/pages/shop-by-scent)[
    
    #### Shop by hair needs](https://www.soapboxsoaps.com/pages/shop-by-hair-needs)

 Cancel Search icon Spinner icon

Translation missing: en.general.icons.icon\_search\_close icon Close search

Search icon Search

    Chevron down icon Shop
    
    Best Sellers

    New Products

    Hair Care

    Bath & Body Care

    Hand Care

    [
    
    #### Shop bundles](https://www.soapboxsoaps.com/collections/bundles)[
    
    #### Shop by scent](https://www.soapboxsoaps.com/pages/shop-by-scent)[
    
    #### Shop by hair needs](https://www.soapboxsoaps.com/pages/shop-by-hair-needs)

Privacy policy
==============

PRIVACY POLICY

INTRODUCTION

Thank you for accessing the SoapBoxSoaps.com Website (“Site”) operated by SoapBox Soaps LLC. We respect your privacy and want to protect your personal information. To learn more, please read this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, and disclose your personal information, as well as the steps we take to ensure the security of your personal information and your options regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. By visiting the Site directly or through another site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and consent to the collection and use of information as discussed herein. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, do not access this Site.

This Privacy Policy applies to the Site. This Privacy Policy does not necessarily apply to any offline collection of your personal information. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices on any website not operated by SoapBox Soaps LLC to which the Site links or that links to the Site.

INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

Our goal in collecting information from you is to provide an efficient and meaningful experience. For example, your personal information allows us to make the site easier to use, help you quickly find information, and alert you to new products we offer.

We collect information from you in several different ways on this Site. We may collect any content, record, or electronic communication of any kind, including without limitation your (1) contact information, (2) financial information, (3) demographic information, and (4) other personal information required to process your application to request services from us, so that we may provide you with the information or services that you request, and so that we may communicate with you and send you information and materials for marketing and other purposes, subject to applicable laws and the terms of the Privacy Policy.

Ordering and Communication

Before using certain parts of the Site or ordering products, you must provide certain information to us, including but not limited to your name, shipping and billing address(es), phone number(s), email address, and credit card number. We use this information for billing, order processing, and order status communication. SoapBox does not sell, rent, trade, license or otherwise disclose your personal or financial information to anyone other than to affiliates SoapBox Soaps LLC’s control, with certain exceptions:

Email Addresses

Several locations of the Site permit you to enter your email address for purposes including but not limited to: to register for a contest or sweepstakes; to request us to notify you of new products; to sign up for email newsletters and special offers. Your participation in a contest, newsletter, sweepstakes, or other email subscription services is completely voluntary, so you have a choice whether to participate and disclose information to us. We use this information to notify contest and sweepstakes winners and to award prizes. By entering a contest or sweepstakes, you may be opting in to receive our email newsletter and special offers and this will be disclosed in the official rules governing the contest or sweepstakes.

Cookies and other Tracking Technologies

This Site uses tracking cookies in order to analyze traffic patterns on the Site. These tracking technologies include, but are not limited to Google analytics and Facebook advertising tracking. These technologies do not identify you other than by your IP address. Cookies and other tracking technologies can be turned off in your browser’s settings, however, portions of the Site may not function if you have disabled cookies. Additionally, the Site maintains a log of IP addresses that visit the Site. This information is used solely for analytical and maintenance activities and will not be linked to any of your personal information.

DATA SECURITY

The Site incorporates physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, including Secure Sockets Layer (“SSL”) for all financial transactions through the Site. We use SSL encryption to protect your personal information online, and we also take several steps to protect your personal information in our facilities. Access to your personal information is restricted. Only employees who need access to your personal information to perform a specific job are granted access to your personal information. Finally, we rely on third-party service providers for the physical security of some of our computer hardware. We believe that their security procedures are adequate. For example, when you visit the Site, you access servers that are kept in a secure physical environment, behind a locked cage and an electronic firewall.

While we use industry-standard precautions to safeguard your personal information, we cannot guarantee complete security. 100% complete security does not presently exist anywhere online or offline.

EFFECTIVE DATE

This Policy is effective as of 19 May 2014. We reserve the right to modify this policy and will update if the policy has been changed or updated.

CONTACT

If you have any questions, requests, or concerns relating to this Policy or to our use of your personal information, do not hesitate to contact us at (347)762-7269 or at service@soapboxsoaps.com.

Explore Chevron down icon
-------------------------

All Collections Chevron down icon
---------------------------------

Follow us
---------

Sign Up For Our Newsletter
--------------------------

Be the first to know about promotions, new products and helpful tips!

 Email address

Sign up

Copyright © 2024 Soapbox.

* Amazon
* American Express
* Apple Pay
* Diners Club
* Discover
* JCB
* Mastercard
* PayPal
* Shop Pay
* Visa

Close icon

Checkmark icon Added to your cart:
----------------------------------

\*\* total\_quantity \*\* | \*\* unit\_price \*\* / \*\* unit\_measure \*\*

Cart subtotal

Lock icon Checkout

Close icon

Close icon

Chevron down icon Chevron down icon

{"themeColor":"#574cd5","iconColor":"#574cd5","showLogo":true,"topBottomPosition":10,"rightLeftPosition":10,"iconSize":"small","iconCustomSize":64,"position":"bottom-right"}
